corning.com 2019-12-06

# Privacy Policy | Corning.com

Corning Incorporated (“Corning,” “we,” “us,” “our”) is committed to safeguarding your data protection online. How your personal data will be processed during your use of Corning’s websites is outlined below.

All of the personal data you submit is collected by Corning Incorporated, and may be shared with one or more local Corning entity (ies) located in your country of residence (according to what you provided in the collection form). Both Corning Incorporated and the relevant local Corning entity(ies) (hereinafter collectively referred to as “Corning”) are acting as Joint Data Controllers in respect of your personal data collected through your use of Corning’s websites. Please click [here](http://www.corning.com/media/worldwide/global/documents/datacontrollers.pdf) to view the names and contact details of all relevant Corning entities.

Corning has implemented a set of [Binding Corporate Rules](http://www.corning.com/worldwide/en/privacy-policy/binding-corporate-rules.html) (“BCRs”) to establish safeguards to ensure that personal data is protected while transferred within the Corning group. The implementation of BCRs provides an adequate level of protection for the personal data transfers carried out from the Corning European Economic Area (EEA) entities to the other Corning entities located in non-EEA countries throughout the world as they are drafted in compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”)1 requirements. The approval of Corning’s BCRs was led by the French supervisory authority, the CNIL, with secondary input from the German state of Hessen and Poland’s supervisory authorities.

From time to time, we may make changes to this notice to reflect changes in our business or to serve you better. Corning will make reasonable efforts to publish any such changes in this notice, such as posting on this website. You should review this notice periodically to stay informed of any changes. Please note the date of the notice below, so that you know when it was last updated.

Corning protects your data protection on Corning.com and related Corning websites through the following basic principles:

**i. Collection and Use of Personal Data**

You will be advised when Corning is collecting information through this website about you or your online preferences and expectations and it will be made clear how that information is to be used.

Our web servers do not collect e-mail addresses unless you provide it to us. However, we do collect generalized information such as the IP address and domain name from which the connection originates. This information is used in the aggregate to measure pages viewed, the amount of time spent on the site, the number of visits, and similar information. We use this information in compliance with our legitimate purpose in improving the contents of this website.

In addition, based on our legitimate interest in improving this website, we utilize various types of “cookies” to maintain a record of your visit. For more information about the types of cookies used by Corning, how they are used, and your options for limiting their use, please review Corning’s Cookies policy by [clicking here](http://www.corning.com/worldwide/en/cookies.html).

Other than information collected through essential cookies (as described in Corning’s [Cookies Policy](http://www.corning.com/worldwide/en/cookies.html)), you will be able to choose whether or not you want to provide such information. For example, some information collected through cookies may also be used for marketing purposes or for tracking and reporting website traffic. If you choose not to provide some information, please be aware that it may not be possible for you to proceed with your chosen business activity with Corning.

When you provide us with information such as names, addresses, phone numbers, e-mail addresses, etc., we will only use them to respond to your inquiries (e.g. provided via the website’s contact form) and manage user established online accounts, based on our legitimate interest in keeping and improving our relationship with you or for specific Corning marketing activities, events, or services upon consent from your part when required

Corning reserves the right to retain electronic communications sent by visitors based on its legitimate interest to detect and interrupt rogue emails. For this purpose, Corning also uses specific technology to forward e-mail and to log e-mail transactions. Logs of e-mail transactions include: date and time of message; name and IP address of the device used to send the e-mail; e-mail address of message originator; and Corning address of recipient

**ii. Disclosure**

Any information collected about you will be kept secure and not shared with third parties, with the exception of Corning affiliates or service providers for the purposes of Corning’s own marketing activities or support of the site, unless you give prior permission for that information to be shared. However, Corning may have to disclose personal data it considers necessary in order to comply with court orders, subpoenas, governmental or law enforcement requests, or to a third party to which ownership of Corning or a Corning affiliate is transferred via an acquisition, merger, sale of assets, etc.

Corning reserves the right to transfer information you provide to other countries in order to share such information with Corning affiliates or service providers. We maintain safeguards reasonably intended to protect your personal data from unauthorized or inappropriate access.

Where the personal data processing involves the transfer of data outside the European Union, Corning ensures that the transfers are carried out in compliance with the GDPR.

Personal data transfers to non EU based Corning entities are covered by the Group’s [Binding Corporate Rules](http://www.corning.com/worldwide/en/privacy-policy/binding-corporate-rules.html), whereas transfers to third-party providers outside the EU are secured through appropriate contractual safeguards such as the EU Commission’s Standard Contractual Clauses, the Privacy Shield certification for transfers to the USA where applicable, or BCRs for Processors. You may request and receive copy of such documents by contacting the Corning Privacy Office as provided in the “Contact Us” section below.

**iii. Retention**

Your personal data processed by Corning are kept in a form which permits your identification for no longer than is necessary for the purposes for which the personal data are processed. To determine the data retention period of your data, we use the following criteria:

\- Where you create an account, we keep your personal data after a period of inactivity defined in accordance with local law and guidance, unless you require us to delete it earlier;

\- Where you contact us for an enquiry, we keep your personal data for the duration needed for the processing of your enquiry;

\- Where you have consented to direct marketing, we keep your personal data used for direct marketing until you unsubscribe or require us to delete it or after a period of inactivity (no active interaction with brands) defined in accordance with local regulations and guidance. In that case, we will only keep the information necessary to handle your right to object in accordance with local regulations and guidance and if you are a client we can keep your personal data but only for client management purpose

\- Where cookies are placed on your computer, we keep it for a period defined in accordance with local regulations and guidance.

**iv. Your rights**

You are allowed to obtain access to the personal data that Corning processes and can make reasonable requests to correct, amend, or delete information, where it is inaccurate.

In the event you choose to delete or thoroughly anonymize your personal data from our database, we may retain a record of your deletion request as well as records indicating the type of information deleted as evidence of our compliance with this Internet Protection Notice.

You can also exercise your rights to obtain the portability of your personal data or to request the restriction of the processing of your personal data.

In addition, whenever Corning processes your personal data based on its legitimate interest, you may at any time object to such processing on legitimate grounds relating to your particular situation.

In addition, you can unsubscribe or opt out of our direct marketing communication at any time. It is easiest to do this by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link in any marketing related email or communication we send you. Otherwise, you can contact us using contact detail below.

Corning does not endorse, nor does it participate in the practice of “spamming” (sending of unsolicited promotional e-mail). If you believe you have received such a message from Corning please contact [privacy@corning.com](mailto:privacy@corning.com).

To submit any of the above mentioned requests, please contact us at [privacy@corning.com](mailto:privacy@corning.com) or at the mailing address listed below. Be sure to include your name and clear instructions regarding any change to your personal data or request to delete your information from our database, and Corning will respond to your message. In case we are unable to complete your request, we will provide you with relevant explanations in due time.

You also have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority if you suspect that Corning is not compliant with applicable data protection rules.. In addition, you can find in the [BCRs](http://www.corning.com/worldwide/en/privacy-policy/binding-corporate-rules.html) of Corning (and more specially in Articles 5.1, 5.4, 6.3, 6.4 and appendix 2) the data protection principles to which Corning is subject and that you have the right to enforce, as a third party beneficiary. Indeed, if you suffer any damage related to the processing of your personal data, you have the rights to obtain redress and, where appropriate, receive compensation as may be ordered by the competent court or Supervisory Authority or as decided according to the internal Corning complaint mechanism, if used.

**v. Children’s personal data**

Corning does not intend to collect information from children under the age of sixteen (16) without the consent of the child’s parent or legal guardian. Children under the age of sixteen (16) should only submit information to Corning with the prior consent of their parent or legal guardian. If your child has submitted personal data to Corning and you would like to request that such information be removed, please contact us as provided below and we will use reasonable efforts to ensure such information is removed.

International visitors to Corning’s websites should be aware that personal data may be transferred to computers in the United States or other locations around the world in order to fulfill your request.

**vi. Security measures applicable to your personal data**

Corning implements all appropriate technical and organizational to ensure a level of security for the personal data appropriate to the risk and, in particular, protect personal data against accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access to. The same level of protection is contractually imposed by Corning on our services providers.

**vii. Miscellaneous**

Corning's websites may contain links to other sites not under the Corning domain names or not owned by Corning. These links are provided solely as a convenience to you. We are not responsible for the content, security, or data protection practices employed by non-Corning websites. Corning does not endorse, warrant, or guarantee the products or services described or offered in these other websites.

Non-personal data you may supply to Corning through Corning websites will not be treated as proprietary or as confidential and Corning assumes no obligation to protect such information from disclosure. Corning may use any such information you supply to respond to inquiries or as part of its marketing activities. Further, the submission of such information to Corning shall not restrict the purchase, manufacture, or use of similar products, services, plans, and ideas by Corning for any purpose whatever and Corning shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute the information to others without restriction.

**viii. Contact us**

If you want to exercise your rights or if you have any questions or comments about this privacy notice, please contact us at:

**Global Data Privacy Office**  
One Riverfront Plaza  
MP-HQ-W1-Z12  
Corning, NY 14831  
(607) 974-9000  

For more information, please use the following links to access the Internet Privacy Data Protection Notice and Global Data Privacy Policy in a variety of languages.
